fxinstructor.com 2009-08-05

# Privacy Policy - Forex Education, Technical Analysis, Trading Strategies

| 

|  | 

## Your privacy is important to us.

FX Instructor strictly adheres to the following principles of data collection.

Please read this page carefully.

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please do not hesitate to [contact us](http://www.fxinstructor.com/eng/support/contact.php) at any time.  
  
---|---  
  
| 

## What information we collect about you:

We collect the following information during the normal course of business:

  * Information gathered from applications, forms and other information that you provide to us.
  * Information about your purchases and customer experience with FX Instructor.
  * Demographic and other general information we obtain that allows us to better serve you.

---|---  
  
| 

## How we use your information:

We use your personal information in the following ways:

  * We use your personal information in order to to properly serve you during the normal course of business.
  * We may also use personal information for auditing, research and analysis to operate and improve our technologies and services.
  * We may share aggregated non-personal information with third parties outside of FX Instructor.
  * We may also use personal information to enable affiliates to properly serve you and receive credit for referral.
  * We may share information with third parties in limited circumstances, including when complying with legal process, preventing fraud or imminent harm, and ensuring the security of our network and services.

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please do not hesitate to [contact us](http://www.fxinstructor.com/eng/support/contact.php) at any time.  
  
---|---  
  
| 

## Do you need help?

Do you have any questions about our privacy policy? Click the link below to find out how to get help.

---|---  
  
|  |
